{
    "subject": "resource/James_Kay_(Kentucky_politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Kentucky",
    "human_readable": "James Kay attended the University of Kentucky.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873364567756653,
            "question": "Was James Kay enrolled in the University of Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9853931069374084,
            "question": "Is James Kay a student at the University of Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9850737452507019,
            "question": "Has James Kay received his education at the University of Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9807610511779785,
            "question": "Did James Kay study at a university in Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650956988334656,
            "question": "Is the University of Kentucky associated with James Kay's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136455059051514,
            "question": "Where did James Kay attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8603779673576355,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that James Kay attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7631229162216187,
            "question": "What university did James Kay go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7564862370491028,
            "question": "At which university did James Kay pursue his studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.643332302570343,
            "question": "What institution of higher learning did James Kay attend?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Kay attended the University of Kentucky.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3557_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At which university did James Kay pursue his studies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3557_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university did James Kay go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3557_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university that James Kay attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3557_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3557_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that James Kay attended the University of Kentucky. In fact, there are multiple mentions of this fact in different files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3557/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3557/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document `dbpedia_3557/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt` mentions that \"Kay earned his BA in history and political science from the University of Kentucky,\" which supports the statement that James Kay attended the University of Kentucky."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}